Your age is 27?
I'm 20.
You have a wife and child?
I live alone.
You like curry?
I like ramen.
CAN PSYCHIC POWERS EXPOSE?
Santa Dodoria sure is something.
So flamboyantly wrong.
There's no way such a young idol
could have a wife and a kid.
Even I can see that.
Is it okay to air that as-is?
Should be okay.
Nobody would be so pissed off
at a local program like this one.
VACANT
CARRYING PASSENGERS
You're Santa Dodoria, aren't you?
I saw you on TV the other day.
Do you really have psychic powers?
Here's fine. Drop me off.
Huh?
It's not like I'm trying to insult you
or anything. I just wanted you to show me.
If you don't wanna die,
hurry on and scram.
Come on now, I thought you brought over
yet another scumbag.
But this one isn't even human.
Sheesh. My grandkid
only brings problems in.
My skin's gonna get dry from all the stress.
Come on. Bring it on.
EPISODE 3
IT'S A GRANNY VS. GRANNY CLASH!
That was close! You're super fast!
But things happened just as I predicted.
I thought you'd come around
to my blind spot.
You fell into the trap
that I had set up beforehand.
If you cross that line, you'll die.
That's a barrier right there.
When you drive a warding nail
inside this circle,
the inside of the circle
turns into a barrier.
But if you drive it outside the circle, the area
outside of the circle becomes the barrier.
The reason you couldn't touch me
was because I was protected by a barrier.
I'll make sure to eat and kill you.
Don't think you can keep me trapped forever.
I don't wanna trap you.
I wanna kill you.
Come on, stand your ground, will ya?
You're gonna cross that line!
What's wrong?
When you're in there, you can't make use
of your speed that you're so proud of.
You scummy old hag!
Did an old hag just call
another old hag a scummy old hag?
That pisses me off.
If you burn me,
this guy that I cursed will die, too.
I'll kill off all scumbags
who deceive my grandkid.
Even if they're human.
Bye.
Scummy old hag!
Okarun!
Hey, you were home?
Shut up. I'm watching
"Bakatono."
Anyway, I have something
to talk about with you.
You went to a spiritual hotspot?
I did.
Not me, but a friend.
Why?
"Why?"
Because we were talking
and that's how things ended up.
"Bakatono"
is Japan's national treasure.
Hey, were you listening?
Anyway, did you see a guy?
He'll be in big trouble
if I'm not around!
If you're talking about the evil spirit,
I killed it.
An evil spirit? What kind?
Did it have glasses on?
Come on, you don't even believe
in ghosts.
Besides, I'm a fake spirit medium.
How long are you gonna hold
that grudge, you scummy old hag.
Something really bad might happen,
so just answer me!
Stop it. Don't believe in those stories.
There are no evil spirits,
and I'm a fake.
Grandma.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
So please tell me.
What did you do to the evil spirit?
Head over to the main shrine.
Scummy old hag!
If something's wrong with Okarun,
I'll never forgive you!
I didn't want to miss my chance.
He was just an occult freak
who simply wanted friends.
It's my fault.
Because I forced him
to go to that place!
I'm sorry, Okarun!
Okarun!
Miss Ayase! I'm so glad!
I thought that I'd murdered you
or something.
Huh?
Wait. Miss Ayase?
Miss Ayase?
You're still alive and well,
scumbag four-eyes!
What? What's up with that?
Well, I’m sorry I'm still alive!
I'm so irritated.
Since when have you
started being friends with monsters?
You scared me!
The curse won't kick in
as long as he's in there.
But one step outside,
and he's back to a monster.
What was that about killing him off?
You lied to me.
You seemed pretty desperate.
You into brats like that?
No way!
Turbo Granny took his you-know-what.
And she told me that as long as she has it,
his curse won't be lifted.
I'm responsible for what happened to him,
so I just want to do something about it.
Oh, I see. So you do like him.
I didn't say that!
Anyway, I can use psychic powers now.
What the hell are you talkin' about?
I went to this place where UFOs show up.
A lot of stuff happened there,
and now I can use powers.
But UFOs don't exist.
I totally get that reaction.
I was just like that until yesterday.
Anyway, it's true
that I can use psychic powers now.
And if I'm not holding back
Okarun's curse with it, he goes wild.
I'm sure psychic powers exist.
I don't know what your criteria
for believing stuff is.
Anyway, Turbo Granny, huh?
You sure got your hands
on a troublesome one.
In the past, she used to be called
Hundred Kilo Granny.
She's a modern yokai monster that
wreaked havoc all over the country.
And I heard such an elusive entity
had been dwelling for some time in that tunnel.
I went over there once to check things out.
KEEP OUT
It was most strange.
I couldn't even get near the tunnel
because of just how strong
the spiritual power was.
You know about location-bound spirits?
They're spirits that stay in particular locations
that they have strong attachments to.
They're basically the strongest
within their territories.
No spirit medium would go up
against a location-bound spirit.
There was a location-bound spirit
inside that tunnel.
Do you know what that means?
Turbo Granny and that location-bound spirit
had fused together.
Don't try to fight against it.
I don't want to lose my dear grandchild.
You're not directly involved with it, either.
So forget about him.
You should return to everyday life.
I wonder what the Ken-san I love
would do in times like this.
When I can't decide, that's what I think.
I've never had regrets by choosing this way.
And if this was Ken-san,
I'm 100% positive he'd go in and help.
So that's what I'm gonna do!
Ken-san, you say?
- You're totally in love with that kid!
- No, that's not what I mean!
I wasn't talking about him!
Hey, she's confessing your love to you.
How do you feel?
I told you that's not what I mean!
I'm talking about the actor!
Looks like I got no choice
if you're gonna go that far.
Go play tag with Turbo Granny.
That thing has absolute confidence
in its running.
A few random taunts
and it's sure to take the challenge.
Now this is where the problem starts.
The location-bound spirit's territory
is all of Shono City.
You have to lure Turbo Granny outside
of the city without getting caught.
If you can drag it away from its territory,
it will get weak and even you guys
will be able to defeat it.
Oh no, look at these feeble legs.
There's no way in hell
I can play tag against Turbo Granny.
Instead of doing something like that,
can't you make something
like those barriers and deal with it?
PEACEFUL PROSPEROUS FAMILY
WARD AGAINST EVIL AND MISFORTUNE
Like putting one up at the tunnel.
I can't do that.
I can't help out to begin with.
Huh? What's up with that?
KAMIGOE CITY
My barrier spells only borrow the powers
of the gods that live on this land.
Once we leave Kamigoe City where we live,
I can't use these powers.
Oh, so we have our own territory, too.
All lands have their own gods.
The problem is whether you're playing
a home or an away game.
In any case, this is the only way
to defeat Turbo Granny.
If you start physically training now,
you should be able to become
fast enough to run away from her.
Are you seriously saying that?
No matter how hard I tried, I couldn't even
make it to the prefecture finals for track meets!
I'm not talking about you.
Huh?
- I'm talking about him.
- Oh, I see!
You're finally including me
into the conversation?
Sorry, I forgot.
But Okarun, you have no stamina.
None at all.
And I have to keep control over your curse.
Then he needs to run piggy-backing Momo.
Miss Ayase, how much do you weigh?
Hey, do ya wanna die?
Oh no, it's just impossible!
My limit for going full strength
in cursed mode is about twice!
Right!
Then train so that you can
always be at full strength.
Get to it. Push-ups, sit-ups, back extensions,
and squats. Five sets, 100 reps each.
- Huh?
- Do it.
And Momo, same goes
for your psychic powers.
You need to power it up
more than what it is now.
As I can't be of any help,
you guys simply have to get stronger.
So I will be training the two of you.
Go to sleep for today.
We'll start tomorrow.
Four-eyes, start your physical training
right now.
Oh, okay.
Your granny is so young.
Isn't she annoying?
Miss Ayase, I'm so sorry.
When I fought that big thing,
I was honestly too desperate
to think of anyone other than myself.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, there's nothing
you could've done about that.
But Miss Ayase, you were different.
You saved me and defeated the monster.
But if something like that happens again,
I'll do my best so that I can save you.
So please don't be disappointed with me.
Please, don't stop being a friend.
I wouldn't be disappointed.
You're overthinking.
Then why did you slam the door earlier?
W-Well, that was...
See, there you go!
You really were disappointed!
I said I wasn't!
But like, I am right now!
You're such a pain!
I'm sorry.
You were pretty awesome
when you were fighting.
But you're kinda dense, Okarun.
I'll probably be saving you next time, too!
You sleep there for today.
I'll bring you a futon right now.
Miss Ayase!
Um, well...
I'm...
really thirsty,
so can I have some water?
Can I take this barley tea?
Sure thing.
We have some shocking news
that just came in!
NEWS FLASH! SHOMA (20) SECRET CHILD SCANDAL
SHOCKING - POPULAR IDOL SHOMA (20)
MAY HAVE A SECRET CHILD.
AGENCY HAS ADMITTED.
It came out into the open
that popular idol Shoma had a secret child!
And his age wasn't 20, but actually 27!
They need to correct his favorite food
from ramen to curry, too!
NEWS FLASH - SHOMA (20) SECRET CHILD FOUND
Furthermore...
...he and his partner...
[LIVE] EMERGENCY SHOMA (20) A SECRET CHILD?
...have not...
BROADCAST SHOMA (20)
SECRET CHILD PRESS CONFERENCE
...formally submitted...
POPULAR IDOL'S SECRET CHILD FOUND
SHOMA (20) ADMITS
...a marriage license.
NEWS FLASH! POPULAR IDOL'S SHOCKING TRUTH...
AGENCY HOLDS EMERGENCY CONFERENCE
I couldn't care less about that news.
Miss Ayase!
Crap! Okarun wants to go
to the bathroom!
Just go.
No, but this is seriously bad news!
If something blocks my view and
I can't see Okarun, my spell on him breaks!
In other words, I have to watch Okarun
as he relieves himself!
Then watch him.
I'd never want to watch!
Who would show you, anyway?
That tramples upon someone else's dignity!
Hey! Don't look away!
Don't you have any good ideas?
Dunno.
How the hell are you holding
the curse back to begin with, anyway?
Let's see...
How do I put it...
It's like I can see an aura around Okarun.
An aura?
And when I crush that aura
with my hands, the aura shrinks.
And the curse subsides, I guess?
Everyone has some kind of aura,
and they come in all sorts of colors.
I see them on the trees
and rocks there too.
I can grab all those auras and move them
at my will, though only in a small area.
I see. I thought psychic powers
were a lot more omnipotent.
Sounds like it's quite limited.
It was a lot more amazing the moment
the powers awoke inside of me.
That was when everything I imagined
turned into reality, like I was invincible!
But that went away real quick.
I can only grab auras and stuff now.
Momo, close your eyes for a bit.
No way. If I do that,
my spell will be lifted.
Basically, the problem
is the reliance on your vision.
Try using all of your senses, such as touch.
The fact that you can grab the aura
means that it's tactile.
So close those eyes
and try feeling the aura with your skin.
Slowly, feel it around you.
So cold.
How am I doing?
Yeah.
He's transformed.
No good.
Well, crap.
That really pushed me close to the limit!
I won't last much longer!
What are you gonna do, Momo?
He's gonna poop any moment.
You're the one who told me to try that!
I don't want to be watched
as I relieve myself!
But I wanna pee in my pants even less!
Hold on!
I'm gonna borrow your bathro—
You've got some nerve to take a dump
in someone else's house, punk!
I'm pretty desperate too, you know!
Why you little...
Who said they'd lend you the bathroom?
Are you an absolute idiot?
I can piss right here if you want!
Let me in on this too!
Don't think you can run faster
than me in this house!
Outta my way!
Or you'll have a disaster!
Not bad, Ken Takakura!
This one is mine!
Not letting you!
This is humiliating.
Says you.
I had looked forward to experiences
unknown until now,
like getting abducted by aliens.
Seriously?
But this is just too much.
I want to hurry up
and be released from this curse.
Momo, you said that you were invincible
when your powers first awoke.
Yeah.
That's likely your original power.
And it seems for some reason,
that power has been sealed off.
What's with that? It sounds kinda cool.
It's a pain in the butt.
You have to unleash it
bit by bit through training,
and we don't know
how long that will take.
Though it's okay because it looks like
that boy's physical makeover will take some time.
I have to be watched while going
to the bathroom for a while?
That's my line...
Grandma, it's here! Turbo Granny!
Grandma?
Damn you! What the hell
are you doing to Grandma?
I'm letting her choose her cause of death.
A heart attack or a stroke.
My curse is contagious through this brat.
Any human this brat sees,
I can curse to death.
Don't underestimate me.
I'm not gonna give you any time.
Come to the tunnel tonight.
Otherwise, I'll use this brat to curse
everyone around there to death.
That's tonight.
Got that?
A nosebleed...
Grandma!
What's this?
You're bleeding from your ears, too!
Does your head hurt or something?
Momo. Let's hear about what just happened.
Am I seriously wearing this?
It's hard to see in front of me.
That's a bulletproof vest
against evil spirits.
Make sure to keep them on.
If you let your guard down,
you'll die quite easily.
I know that! Despite how we look,
we did defeat aliens!
There's no such thing as aliens.
Quit horsing around.
Oh, okay.
You bring all the trouble home in the first place
because you're like that.
You've never listened to me
ever since you were a little kid.
Man, so annoying!
The old hag's nagging is annoying.
Let's go, Okarun.
Momo!
What now? You're so naggy.
Don't die.
Yeah.
I beg of you.
Please, protect those two.
Why are we going by train?
It's too far by bicycle!
And you don't want to use up your stamina
before we get there!
You seriously aren't getting off
the hook, Turbo Granny!
- I'm sorry, this is all for...
- No way!
That hag tried to hurt something dear to me!
I'm gonna beat Turbo Granny into a pulp!
Hold on, Miss Ayase!
You shouldn't do that here!
I want to hurry up and take these off.
Is it okay to do that?
It's a battle uniform to protect yourself
from evil spirits, right?
Your grandmother said keep it on.
Who the hell would wear something like that?
Fashion is the battle uniform for gyarus!
I can't get hyped up unless I wear
the clothes I want to wear!
Why are you smiling?
Isn't this kinda fun?
Not at all. I feel like I'm about to puke.
Who's a gaudy old hag, ya scummy old hag!
What's got into you?
Turbo Granny called me
a gaudy old hag the other day!
Huh? That really happened?
You were kinda crazy
from that curse, Okarun!
All right, let's go!
Next episode,
"Kicking Turbo Granny's Ass."
EPISODE 4
KICKING TURBO GRANNY'S ASS
But in the end,
it's a bit embarrassing to go by train.